Deepak K. Bhaskar

E-mail: deepucsait@gmail.com

Website: https://deepanveshana.github.io/aboutme

Phone: 7045880819

Address: "Sriniketana" NH66, near New Basha Transport, Kundapura-576201, Udupi district, Karnataka

SUMMARY

An entusiastic Software Developer with **more than 3 years of experience** in application and website development. Looking for an opportunity wherein I can showcase my experience and work in a competative task and there by contributing towards organization's success.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Robosoft Technologies

Jul 2018 — Present

Hybrid Application Developer

Working as a hybrid application developer in Robosoft Technologies, Udupi.

Currently working for a renowned Mutual Fund distributor's responsive web portal and mobile application (iOS and Android). My key responsibilities are to develop the application end-to-end, deciding the technologies to choose and to suggest the changes in the design to client.

Majesco Software and Solutions India Pvt Ltd

Jun 2015 — Jul 2018

Full Stack Developer

Worked as a Full Stack Developer at Majesco for exact 3 years. Worked in multiple projects and the major one is for US based client's Insurance portal. Technologies which I have worked on are Angular JS, JAVA, Oracle SQL, Spring, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Require JS.

PROJECTS

Axillo (Robosoft Technologies)

Jul 2018 - Present

Axillo is a project of Axis Mutual Fund. The project is abut developing hybrid applications (web portal and mobile applications) for their distributor where they can manage and update their client list as well as carrying out their transactions.

Role: Hybrid Application Developer (Ionic 4 + Angular 6)

Technologies: Ionic wrapper with Angular 6, Bootstrap, Cordova.

Team size: 4

Responsibilities: Designing the project structure, deciding the technologies to be used and developing the UI side of the project end-to-end.

New York Life Insurance (Majesco Ltd)

Jul 2018 - Present

It is an online portal for New York Life Insurance catering the life insurance facilities for their insurers. The insurers can be an employee of New York Life Insurance or a group of TPA's client. It also has an admin portal of underwritters to approve/reject the online insurance applications.

Role: Full Stack Developer (Angular1.3/Angular 4, Java/Spring, Oracle SQL)

Technologies: Backbone JS, Angular 1.3, Angular 4, HTML5, CSS3, Java/Spring, Require JS, Bootstrap, Oracle SQL, Javascript/jQuery.

Team size: 15

Responsibilities: Leading the UI team of size 2 and guiding them and building UI screens based on client's requirements and supporting the same.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Frameworks

Angular 1.3, Angular 4, Angular 6, Spring, Ionic-Cordova

Web Technologies

HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Require JS

Back-end technologies

Java, Oracle Sql

Subversion Control tools

SVN, Git, Gitlab

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering

Sep 2009 - Jun 2013

Jun 2006 – Jun 2008

Dr Ambedkar Institute of Technology, Bengaluru

Graduated with BE degree with majors in Computer Science with an overall aggregate of 67%.

Pre-University College

R.N.S PU college, Kundapura

Completed my Pre-University with a percentage of 84 in Class 12. Computer Science was my main subject in the course. Was also a speaker of the parliament in College.

Class 10 Jun 2007 — Jun 2008

V.K.R. Acharya Memorial English High School, Kundapura

Completed class 10 with an aggregate of 91.52%.

INTERESTS

 $Painting, Sketching \ (\ ref: \underline{https://thepatronusart.wordpress.com}\), \ Blogger, \ Clay\ Modeling.$

SOCIAL SITES

 ${\bf Portfolio\ Site:}\ \underline{\rm https:} \underline{\rm deepanveshana.github.io/aboutme}$

Blog: https://thepatronusart.wordpress.com http://lostandfoundcode.blogspot.com

Github: https://github.com/deepanveshana

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/deepak-bhaskar-a7259257/

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Full Name: Deepak Kota Bhaskar

Mother's Name: Girija Devadiga

Father's Name: Bhaskar Devadiga

Date of Birth: 18 October 1990

Marital Status: Unmarried

Permanent Address: "Sriniketana" NH66

near New Basha Transport

Kundapura-576201, Udupi district, Karnataka

SUMMARY

I hereby declare that all the information provided here are true to the best of my knowledge.

Date:

Signature: